Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Praise the Lord, Church!
My name is Ogbonna Iwuogbonnaya.
I am from Abia State, Nigiera, living in Libya.
My testimony goes like this: I am a gas welder by profession.
One day, a customer brought me an item to work on in my shop.
When I started the work, I had already checked to see if the gas was working properly.
However, immediately when I started working, the gas exploded.
As it exploded, I didn't know again where I was.
I was very confused to the extent that I could not open my eyes.
I called my driver who took me to a private hospital.
When we reached there, they said they couldn't do anything and directed me to another hospital.
When I reached there, I met more than five Libyan citizens sitting there with different cases.
After waiting more than thirty minutes, I told my driver that we had to leave.
The driver was confused and asked why because he knew I was in severe pain.
I couldn't even sit down or touch my face because the pain was too much for me.
I couldn't bear the pain and told my driver that we should go.
You mean when you were being taken to the first hospital, you were completely rejected?
Yes.
Because your face was completely damaged, burnt?
Exactly.
And they couldn't attend to you?
From there, you were taken to the second hospital?
Yes.
When you got there, there were no doctors to attend to your case.
Exactly.
So what happened from there?
From there, I remembered that I had Morning Water in my house; I used to watch Emmanuel TV.
I had seen God using Prophet T.B. Joshua to heal many people.
I decided to return to my house.
The pain was so much that I didn't even know where I was.
The pain was so severe that I couldn't even touch my face.
More than five people were fanning me even though I was in an air-conditioned room.
You mean the burning sensation was so severe?
So severe.
That you could not even touch your face?
Not at all.
You couldn't even open your eyes?
I could not open my eyes; I even thought that my eyes had been blinded.
You thought you were blind?
I thought I had been blinded.
When I ministered the Morning Water on my face, immediately my eyes opened!
I said, "What is this?"
So, the first time that you ministered the Morning Water on your face, you could open your eyes clearly?
Is this what you are saying?
It was when I ministered the Morning Water that I was able to see what had happened to me.
Immediately after ministering the Morning Water, I took a mirror and looked at myself.
I said, "Oh God!" I thanked God.
I continued ministering the Morning Water and gradually, without taking medication,
my face started healing and the wound drying.
Put your hands together for Christ Jesus!
Indeed, we are serving a mighty God.
We want you to show us - we can see some pictures on the board next to you.
Can you please tell us what these pictures stand for.
This is a picture of when the incident happened.
On the screen of our television, we can see the picture of when the incident took place - when he was affected.
When I began ministering the Morning Water, my face started peeling, as you can see in this picture.
So that is when the burnt skin started peeling off, after the ministration of the Morning Water?
Yes.
I even thought that my skin would not be smooth again as I had seen others who faced a similar problem
and they died or their face was condemned.
To God be the glory, through the Morning Water, the skin on my face became normal.
I am here now; I am a living testimony!
I even left my beard to grow because I never thought I would grow a beard again.
You said what? Please repeat what you said.
Put your hands together for Christ Jesus!
Indeed, we can imagine! How can a beard grown again on a burnt face? - By no means.
Sir, we want to ask you one more question:
If not for the medium of the Morning Water, what do you think would have happened to your face
that we are seeing glowing now?
I would have had to undergo plastic surgery.
But to God be the glory, what happened to your face?
I thank God so much that I'm okay now and strong. Even my hand that was burnt is okay now.
Everything is completely restored?
Yes.
To God be the glory. Let us put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
What can you now say about this powerful medium of the Morning Water that God Almighty has used
to restore your skin and to replace it to its original position?
I used to tell people that God sent the Morning Water through Prophet T.B. Joshua for us to use.
The Morning Water is something I even find difficult to explain.
There was a boy who was brought to my house in Libya with stomach pain.
He couldn't eat; he would immediately vomit anything that entered his mouth.
But when I ministered the Morning Water to him, he immediately ate biscuits and took a drink.
Within a small time, he asked for rice - and this was a boy who couldn't eat for three days.
Anything he put into his mouth before, he would vomit it immediately.
So, the Morning Water is a great thing God Almighty sent to us through Prophet T.B. Joshua.
To God be the glory! We know we are blessed.
What advice do you now have for the viewers watching you and those listening to you right now?
Praise the Lord!
My advice to viewers, especially those who are watching me in Libya -
on Sundays we don't have to go to work in Libya and always worship with Emmanuel TV -
my advice is to believe in God because with Him, all things are possible.
I did not believe before that I would be like this today but through Emmanuel TV and the Morning Water,
I am a living testimony today; I thank God.
Amen.
Can you please touch your face for the last time?
You said you were unable to touch your face before.
Can you please touch your face and tell us if you are still feeling any pain?
Nothing. No pain. Now I am okay.
Are you feeling any pain?
Nothing. I'm alright.
Everything is fresh?
Everything is fresh.
Wholesome, for the glory of God.
Put your hands together for Christ Jesus!
We thank God Almighty for this wonderful testimony you have shared with us.
We believe this has really encouraged us and has lifted up our faith in Christ Jesus.
We want to encourage you that now that you have been set free, healed for the glory of God,
continue to live your life to please Jesus Christ, and we pray that He would give you the grace to
maintain this wonderful healing, in Jesus' mighty name.